Graduation's coming up soon.
Yeah.
Hey, Yuki...
You haven't been taking
your stuff home, huh.
Yep.
C'mon, I'll help out.
Show me what you wanna keep.
--Okay.
--And throw all those papers out!
Okay.
Hori's acting like Yoshikawa's mom.
Ishikawa-kun, you sure
have a lot of stuff.
So do you.
You guys are such pigs.
You're supposed to take
stuff home every day!
Do you have a free hand, Hori-san?
--Huh?
--Could ya help me out here, Hori?
Me, too!
What?
I swear, you guys...
Your arms are so strong, though!
Damn, Hori-san, you had
this much crap piled up?!
No, these guys did!
"Take all personal belongings home today!"
Wait, you have like, no stuff at all.
Right? 'Cause I was a good boy
and took it home every day!
"Iura was doing his job
and you guys weren't?"
Right? 'Cause I was a good boy
and took it home every day!
"Iura was doing his job
and you guys weren't?"
Please, Hori-san.
Don't look at me like that.
Oh, I've got this CD!
Wait, really?! This must've been one
I forgot to give back to you. Sorry.
Oh, snap, yeah, I'll take it.
Sorry, man.
Come to think of it, I have
some DVDs I borrowed off you.
Huh?
Same here.
What?
Well, there goes my sweet,
light-handed commute.
Sorries!
All good.
You still have way more
than all of us, Yuki.
A couple of us stronger guys could
help you carry it down to the entrance.
Like me, Ishikawa, or...
...Hori-san!
What'd I do?!
H-He means you're so dependable, Hori-san!
He didn't mean anything insulting by it!
"Horimiya"
"I Would Gift You The Sky"
Remi, could you get the trash...?
"Fun Spring Trips!"
She's distracted again.
What're you reading? A travel mag?
Uh-huh.
Is that a zoo?
You wanna go see a big herd of giraffes?
I mean, sure, but...
Sengoku-kun, Yanagin!
You wanna go to the zoo, too, yeah?
Which one? The same one as before?
No, a different one.
Whoa, this is pretty far away.
We'd have to make it a two-day trip.
We'd need a car.
And a hotel.
So we can go if we get a car and a hotel?!
Don't encourage her, boys.
You're going to make her
think this might actually happen.
--She's such a mom.
--Okay, mom.
A car, though... Sure
would be nice to have one.
We could get to way more places.
I can't wait to get my license.
Huh?
If I had a car, I could take you anywhere
you wanted, Remi, not just that zoo.
O-Oh. Yeah, that's right.
Perhaps this isn't about going
to the zoo, but something else?
What do you mean?
I'm gonna go buy a drink!
Hold it, Remi.
What's going on? What's bothering you?
Nothing!
We won't know unless you tell us.
Grab her, Sengoku-kun.
It's nothing, I swear!
So tell us what it is.
H-Hey, uh...
If you won't let us help you,
then you're going to force my hand.
I'll show Yanagi-kun what you look
like with your cheeks all stretched out.
K-K-Kono-san?!
Fine, do it! Get it over with!
Ayasaki-san?!
What on Earth is going on?!
Is this something you do often?!
Certainly you can't force
her to talk like... like...
Oh, wow, her cheeks...
Kono-san, Ayasaki-san
can't talk like this!
Sengoku-kun, please make her stop!
Take a good, long look. You don't
get to see her like this that often.
Why?!
Are you okay?
I'm fine. That felt nice.
It did?
Look, it's not bothering me or anything.
I just figured we could go somewhere
fun while we're still in high school.
But as soon as you talked
about getting a license,
I realized he could use it
to go really far away.
Or he could just use it
to do everyday errands.
"Getting a car = going away???"
Or he could just use it
to do everyday errands.
"Getting a car = going away???"
Oh...
"Fun Spring Outings"
I mean, we don't have to go
to the zoo or anything.
You don't need to worry.
We'll be friends forever.
Really? You won't treat me like
a stranger the second you graduate?
Not at all. That'd be a lot
of effort on our part.
Here's an idea.
Huh?
Once I get my license, would you
all like to go on a road trip?
That sounds nice. Where would we go?
L-Let's go to the ocean!
Are you fond of the ocean, Kono-san?
I-I wanna go to the ocean, too!
We can go swimming!
I won't swim. I just
want to see the ocean.
Then that's what we'll
do after graduation.
Let's go to the zoo, too, Yanagin!
Why don't you get your
license, too, Ayasaki-san?
Because I call shotgun!
No fair, Remi!
Sengoku-kun...
Hori-san?
Earth to Hori-san...
She's fast asleep.
Makes sense after carrying
all that heavy stuff.
Miyamura.
Yeah! I'm here!
Guess she just wanted a pillow.
She's frowning in her sleep.
She makes that face a lot, huh.
Hori-san, you're going to end up
with wrinkles on your forehead.
She eats a lot, moves a lot,
and sleeps a lot.
She's so funny.
I hope these days never end.
Even after graduation.
If that tiny happenstance
hadn't occurred...
If it hadn't...
If it hadn't happened...
Are our graduation essays due
on the last day of school?
Oh, crap, I totally forgot!
They took our graduation
picture super long ago, huh.
I have no idea what I look like in mine.
--I was next to a guy
I'd never spoken to before.
--Ishikawa! Let's head home!
--I was next to a guy
I'd never spoken to before.
--Ishikawa! Let's head home!
--It was totally awkward. I don't
even remember if I said anything.
You're in the same class, though!
Sorry.
Oh, it's okay.
You wanna go to karaoke today?
How'd your sister do on that exam?
Didn't pass.
Oof. That sucks.
Oh, Sengoku-kun!
Kono-san?
I was just in the student council room...
Oh, did you finish cleaning?
Yeah, I did.
Got it.
C'mon, Sakura, let's go!
Okay.
She looked so much better with long hair.
He's so unfriendly.
C'mon, hurry!
Hey, Remi! Don't rush me!
Oh, right! You know that shop
you told us about before?
Sakura?
Do you know them?
Huh? Oh, no, I don't.
Taking my stuff home is such a pain...
Ugh, taking my stuff home is such a pain.
I should've brought it home ages ago.
I should've just brought it home ages ago.
--All students, please head home
so the all-staff meeting may begin.
--Kyoko-chan! Let's go!
--All students, please head home
so the all-staff meeting may begin.
--Yeah, I'm coming.
--All students, please head home
so the all-staff meeting may begin.
We have a whole 'nother
week until graduation...
I hope it'll be warmer for graduation.
For real.
Kyoko-chan!
Did you see that guy?!
He was a mega hottie!
Wait, where? He a third year?!
Man, I didn't see!
Whoa, someone's still here?
Gotta find my phone...
Whew, found it.
Hey.
You dropped this.
Huh? Wh-What?
This was on the floor.
Looks like an earring.
Is it yours?
I-I don't know!
Hey, dude!
The hell? What a weirdo.
Somehow...
My high school days feel like
they amounted to nothing.
This is all hypothetical.
I know there's no point considering it.
But it wasn't hypothetical for you.
Yeah.
Miyamura?
Sorry, I was spacing out.
You okay? What's got you all spaced out?
Just thinking.
So many coincidences brought me here.
What would it be like if
one of them didn't happen?
Sounds like the fact that we're here
together now is the work of fate.
Maybe.
It was never completely
unfathomable, but it's real.
You're here with me.
Everyone is with me.
I'm here with them now.
Even if the "fate" you
mentioned doesn't really exist,
I'm sure the world would slowly but surely
move in the direction I want it to.
"63rd Graduation Ceremony"
Next, the farewell address from our
graduating student representative,
"Graduation"
Next, the farewell address from our
graduating student representative,
"Graduation"
Kakeru Sengoku-kun.
Yes, ma'am.
Nice going, me.
Hello, everyone.
--Spring is upon us,
--That dummy!
and so, too, is the graduation day for
the 63rd class of Katagiri High School.
All graduating students,
please return to your classrooms.
Miyamura-kun, you little punk!
I'm sorry! I didn't do it on purpose!
Yo, Miyamura!
Nice sneeze!
It was not nice!
He's so scary!
Sorry, Ishikawa-kun!
Shoot, I lost him!
C'mon, dude, should the graduating student
speaker be sprinting through the halls?
Nice speech, by the way.
So what were you chasing Miyamura for?
What do you think I was chasing him for?!
I've gotta apologize to him later.
Nice day out.
You're having fun.
Yup.
You cut your hair.
They found out about the
piercings. And my tattoos.
I have a lot of friends,
plus a girlfriend.
You finally looked at me.
Sorry.
I promise I won't pretend
you're not there anymore.
I'll disappear for you.
Congrats on graduating.
There he is! C'mon, Miyamura,
we're gonna take a class photo!
You gotta hurry back, or...
What's up?
Nothing.
The wind's so strong today.
Ugh, where the hell is our class?
"Photo Duty"
Sensei, let's take a picture together!
I want one, too!
Aww, well, okay, I guess.
You're supposed to take
pictures of all of us, Yasuda!
Why would I take pictures of guys?
I'll grab a snapshot of you
with my eyes. There, done.
Oh, come on! This is a big life moment!
Get a picture of us, please!
Hori-senpai!
I'm so sad I won't get to see you anymore!
What's up?
Y-You can still come over to see me!
Really?!
Not too often, though!
It's her last day.
Might as well let her have it, then.
Our last day, huh...
I'm looking for Remi, have you seen her?
Oh, Ayasaki? No, I haven't.
Oh.
Hey, so...
So, uh-- Sorry, I just...
Thank you.
I had so much fun this year. Really.
I had the best time of my life,
and part of that was
because of you, Ishikawa-kun.
I like you, Ishikawa-kun.
And I like Yoshikawa-san, too.
I'll never forget you.
Same. Neither will I.
Well, good. Thanks.
Yeah, same.
Bye, then!
Take care. See you again soon!
See you later!
Guess she's trying to leave
her feelings behind at school.
Goodbye.
"BA-DUMP"
Oh! Congratulations on graduating!
Hey, you graduated, too! Congrats!
Thank you!
Oh, right! I needed to tell you something.
Wh-What?!
"BA-DUMP"
I'd like to go somewhere
with everyone after graduation.
You mean as a group?
Yeah. We had this conversation
with the student council the other day.
It made me think, once I get my license...
All of us best buds could travel!
--We'll take Miyamura-kun,
Hori-san, Kono-san...
--Best buds.
--We'll take Miyamura-kun,
Hori-san, Kono-san...
--Just the same as always.
--We'll take Miyamura-kun,
Hori-san, Kono-san...
--Sure.
--Huh?
Sounds great! Let's do it!
Oh, good!
Thanks for offering to drive!
Huh?
Nothing's going to change after
graduation, and if it does, that's fine.
We'll still be friends.
Now there's my special boy!
Kyosuke-san!
Whoa, is that Miyamura-kun's dad?!
He's so young!
They look so similar!
Similar how?
I wanna get a picture
with my wonderful kid!
Okay, let me get Hori-san--
Why the hell are you here, Dad?! Huh?!
I'm here to have Dad fun!
Get out of here before someone
sees you in this ridiculous outfit!
Miyamura! Where's your mom and dad?!
They were here for a bit,
but had to head home for work.
Man, why you gotta be so mad?
Shut up and get lost!
C-C'mon, now...
Okay, you're good!
You serious, Iura?
Dead serious, dude.
Big brother!
Hey, Moto, you came?
--Yeah.
--Whoa, is this your little sister?
Yup!
You come to pick your big brother up?
Mom said she wanted you home early.
Plus I figured I could see what
my new school would be like.
Wow, really?!
God, that ceremony was so long!
Why'd they talk so much?
Okey-dokey, let's get
our butts home, Moto!
That's all, folks! Bye bye!
Nice to see Iura peppy till the end.
All's right with the world.
Big brother.
Yes, little sister?
Is it really you?
Yep, it's me.
Miyamura!
We're gonna go get sushi, wanna come?!
I'm in!
Sweet! Let's head out, then.
Kyosuke's gonna be so thrilled,
like, annoyingly so.
Okay!
There's no distance between us.
I've never been this
close to a person before.
There's no boundary between us.
I used to be terrified of that.
I was so scared of this, Hori-san.
You know,
I had no idea
that I could feel
so many different emotions.
I don't think either of us knew
how scary or nerve-wracking being
yourself around others could be.
But you made me realize all of it.
What can I do for you?
How can I make you smile?
You're so much stronger
than I think you are,
and you're so much weaker
than I feel you are.
You're delicate.
You're fragile.
That's why wherever you go,
bright, sunny days follow after.
For years, the only person
I knew this well was myself.
I never knew a world
like this even existed.
Thank you for shattering my reality.
Thank you for wanting a future with me.
What can I do for you?
How can I repay you for what you've done?
C'mon, Miyamura!
Oh.
The spring sky is bluer
than I've ever seen.
If only I could gift you
this wonderful sky.
No, I know what you'd like better.
A cake with lots of whipped cream on top.